Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
- Series III. Clients R-Y
  - Riordon Paper Company Limited Location: Junction of Ottawa and Rouge Rivers,(Prescott or Hawkesbury, Ontario, Canada)
    - Preliminary report on location of an industrial village - General Plan, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 530
    - Description unspecified, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1501
    - Map of the Town of Hawkesbury, 1900 (Folder 45)
      Sheet # 1558
      Scale: 1"=200'
    - Proposed mill-site at Rouge river, 1910 (Folder 45)
      Sheet # 1559
    - Survey of property, 1907 (Folder 45)
      Sheet # 1560
      Scale: 1"=80'
    - Sketch of location of an industrial village at the juncture of the Ottawa and Rouge rivers., Undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1951
    - Birds' eye perspective: A preliminary report on the location of an industrial village at the junction of the Ottawa and Rouge rivers, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1952
    - Suggested types of architecture… industrial village..., 1910 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1953
    - Initial village… industrial village, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1954
    - Approximate sketch survey... Industrial village, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1955
  - Ritts, J. V. Location: Butler, Pennsylvania
    - Extracts from field book #32 showing location of N. W. corner of property, Undated (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1109
    - Road profiles, 1919 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1110
    - Road sections, 1919 (Box 40)
      Sheet # 1111
    - Preliminary road sections, Undated (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1112
    - Road profiles - McKeam Street extension, 1928 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1113
    - Road layout - Southern subdivision of property, 1929 (Box 40)
      Sheet # 1114
      Format: Sepia on Gridded profile paper
    - Plan and profile of Boulevard, 1917 (Box 40)
      Sheet # 1115
    - Road profiles, 1919 (Box 40)
      Sheet # 1116
    - Sketch outline of roads and topography (1), 1914 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1117
    - Sketch outline of roads and topography (2), 1914 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1118
    - Road details, 1928 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1119
    - Study for subdivision (Roads and Planting), 1929 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1120
    - Plan showing location of Ritts' Residences, Undated (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1121
    - Partial plan of subdivision, Undated (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1122
    - Layout and revisions of streets - Northern portion of Borough of Butler, 1917 (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1123
    - Sketch plan - Extensions of McKean street, 1918 (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1124
    - Sketch showing extension of McKean street to connect with property of Ritts, J. V., 1919 (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1125
      Condition:Poor, Oversized
    - Survey of property - showing location of N.W. corner of property, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1126
    - Sketch plan showing skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1127
    - Sketch showing connection of property of Ritts, J. V. to Borough of Butler, 1919 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1128
    - Rough outline of streets and topography, Undated (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1129
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1130
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1131
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1132
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1133
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1134
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1135
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1136
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1137
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1138
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1139
    - Skeleton outline of roads and topography, 1915 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1140
    - Sketch plan - Location of Property, 1914 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1141
    - Sketch plan - Location of Property, 1914 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1142
    - Sketch plan - Location of Property, 1914 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1143
    - Sketch plan - Location of Property, 1914 (Box 41)
      Sheet # 1144
    - Sketch plan - Location of Property, 1914 (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1145
    - Extension of McKean Street to connect with property of Ritts, J. V., 1919 (Folder 39)
      Sheet # 1146
    - Sketch plan - Extensions of McKean street, 1918 (Folder 39)
      Sheet # 1147
  - Roberson, Alonzo Location: Binghamton, New York
    - Residence front elevation, Undated (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1485
    - Residence south elevation, Undated (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1486
    - Residence rear elevation, Undated (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1487
    - Residence north elevation, Undated (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1488
    - Residence first floor plan, Undated (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1489
    - Arrangement of grounds, Undated (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1490
    - South elevation, Undated (Folder 44b)
      Sheet # 1491
      Note:Handwritten text on back
    - Detail garden wall and steps, 1904 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1492
    - Plan for buildings and grounds, Undated (Folder 44b)
      Sheet # 1493
    - Present conditions of estate, Undated (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1494
    - Detail of wall, 1908 (Folder 44b)
      Sheet # 1495
    - Description Description unspecified, Undated (Folder 44b)
      Sheet # 1496
    - Detail of wall and stair in garden, 1908 (Folder 44b)
      Sheet # 1497
    - Arrangement of grounds, 1908 (Folder 44b)
      Sheet # 1498
      Format: Linen 0/5
    - Planting plan, 1908 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1499
    - Arrangement of grounds, 1908 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1500
    - Wall section drawing, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1569
    - Sketch of garden and residence, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1655
    - Iron flower boxes and plant names, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1656
      Format: Graph paper
    - Wall and stair details in garden, 1908 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1657
    - Sketch of urn For garden wall, 1916 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1663
    - Details of pergola and garden accessories, 1908 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1664
    - Profiles of wall about garden, 1908 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1665
    - Fences, Undated (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 2043
  - Robinson, A. Location: Unspecified
    - Perspective sketch in Garden, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 849
  - Robinson, Mary B. Location: Wellsboro, Pennsylvania
    - Basement plan, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 697
      Note:Townsend & Fleming; by architect Wm. H. Miller
    - First story plan, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 698
    - Second story plan, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 699
    - Roof plan, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 700
    - Front elevation, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 701
    - North elevation, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 702
    - West elevation, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 703
    - South elevation, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 704
    - Pergola details, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 705
      Scale: 1/4"=1'; Full
      Format: Ink on vellum
    - Details of fence, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 706
    - Details of veranda rail, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 707
    - Sketch details of brick walls, 1908 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 708
    - Sketch plan for garden, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 709
    - Pergola details, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 710
    - Pergola details, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 711
    - Notes on Grading, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 712
    - Sketches for garden, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 713
    - Staking notes and sketches, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 714
    - Planting plan, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 715
    - Plan of arrangement of grounds, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 716
    - Plan of general arrangement of grounds, 1907 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 717
    - Plan of residence - Exterior walls only, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 718
    - Grading plan, likely, Undated (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 719
      Condition:Poor - Torn in half
  - Sachs, Edward Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - End elevation of residence, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 578
    - Entrance elevation - 2nd revision, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 579
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 580
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 581
    - Entrance elevation - 3rd revision, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 582
    - Service wing elevation, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 583
    - Garden elevation, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 584
    - Profile of roadways - Haas-Sachs Estate, 1912 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 585
  - Sachs, M. D. Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Ground floor plan of proposed residence, Undated (Box 21)
      Sheet # 519
    - Ground floor plan of proposed residence, Undated (Box 21)
      Sheet # 520
    - Ground floor plan of proposed residence, Undated (Box 21)
      Sheet # 521
    - Roof plan - Proposed residence, Undated (Box 21)
      Sheet # 522
  - Sacks (possibly Sachs) Location: Unspecified
    - Elevations of Residence, Undated (Box 20)
      Sheet # 493
  - Sawyer, George P. Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Planting along front wall, 1928 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1517
  - Schmidt, Mme. Traugott Location: Grosse Pointe, Michigan
    - Alternative sketch #3 for entry, 1927 (Box 33)
      Sheet # 842
    - Perspective sketch of Entry, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 844
      Format: Pencil and Crayon on Tracing paper
    - Preliminary Sketch # 1 of Entry, 1927 (Box 33)
      Sheet # 845
    - Alternative Sketch # 2 of Entry, 1927 (Box 33)
      Sheet # 846
  - Scripps, William E. Location: Orion, Michigan
    - Garden to north-east of residence (H. S.), 1928 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1712
      Note:(H. S.)
    - A sketch perspective of Garden and service to Northeast of house (H. S.), 1926 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1713
  - Sears, Horace A. Location: Weston, Massachusetts
    - Details of pergolas in garden, 1902 (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1869
  - Shepherd, Bruce Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Window schedule, wall sections, details, 1931 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 558
    - Door sections, new transom bar finial, Undated (Box 23)
      Sheet # 559
      Scale: Full; 3/4"=1'
    - Ceiling details, Undated (Box 23)
      Sheet # 560
    - Details of cast iron porch, Undated (Box 23)
      Sheet # 561
    - Kitchen plan and elevations, 1931 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 562
    - Butler's pantry plan and elevations, 1931 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 563
    - Flower room - Details of elevation "D", 1931 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 564
    - Silent pantry, flower room arcade - plans and elevations, 1931 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 565
    - Woman's and men's room, 1931 (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 566
    - Dining room plan and elevations, 1931 (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 567
    - Two stone shelves at entrance, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1373
    - Summer House floor, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1374
    - Overport and mirror, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1375
    - Iron facing, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1376
    - Jambs, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1377
    - Glazing for doors #108 and #123, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1378
    - Molding, Cornice, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1379
    - Corner posts, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1380
    - Olds, Caps, Undated (Folder 42b)
      Sheet # 1381
    - Details of glazing, center panel, doors #108 and #123, 1932 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1382
    - Over-mantel, Living room, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1383
      Scale: 1 1/2"=1'; Full
    - Gate, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1384
    - Details of kennels, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1385
    - Tree plan, likely, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1386
    - Entrance gates, posts and walls, 1931 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1387
      Scale: 1/4"=1'; 1/8"=1'
    - Plan of landscape development, 1932 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1389
  - Sherwin, John Location: Willoughby, Ohio
    - Additions to the residence - First floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 532
    - Additions to the residence - Second floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 533
    - Additions to the residence - First floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 534
      Condition:Poor - Only half of plan remains
    - Sketch of existing structure, Undated (Box 21)
      Sheet # 535
    - Detail of paneling for Dining room, 1921 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 536
    - Interior elevations of sleeping porch, Undated (Box 21)
      Sheet # 537
    - Additions to the residence - First floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 538
    - Additions to the residence - Second floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 539
    - Additions to the residence - First floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 540
    - Additions to the residence - Second floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 541
    - Cornice detail - New dining room, 1921 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 542
    - Interiors of new living room, 1921 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 543
    - Basement plan and details, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 544
    - Sketch plan of area about entrance, 1921 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 545
    - Additions to the residence - First floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 546
    - Additions to the residence - Second floor, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 547
    - North elevation of East wing addition, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 548
    - West elevation of East wing addition, 1920 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 549
    - Details of rebuilt main stairs - Alternative "B"., 1921 (Box 21)
      Sheet # 550
    - Basement plan and details, 1920 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 551
    - Second floor plan - East wing addition, 1920 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 552
    - First floor plan - East wing addition, 1920 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 553
    - Existing conditions - Partial first floor plan, 1920 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 554
    - Decorative details, 1921 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 555
    - Second floor plan, 1920 (Box 23)
      Sheet # 556
    - Existing conditions - Elevations, Undated (Box 23)
      Sheet # 557
    - Tentative floor plan including alterations, Undated (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 568
      Scale:
    - Elevations in new kitchen, 1925 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 569
    - Revisions of service and servants cottage, 1925 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 570
    - Sketch of first floor plan, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 571
    - Elevation of gate, 1917 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 572
    - Perspective studies for office, 1925 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 573
    - Studies for office, 1925 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 574
    - Weather-vane on maid's cottage, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 575
    - Sketch of gates, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 576
    - Partial layout of house and service quarters, Undated (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 577
    - Elevation - Cupboard between living and dining rooms, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1213
      Scale: 1 1/8"=1'
    - Elevation - Garden gate, 1924 (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1214
    - Post details, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1215
    - Detail of fascia's for Venetian blinds in sleeping porch, 1921 (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1216
    - Gates on path to house, 1922 (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1217
    - Full size detail of fascia for exterior venetian blinds in dining room, 1922 (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1218
    - Plan and elevation of Laundry, 1922 (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1219
    - Balustrade details, Undated (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1220
    - Interior elevations - Sun room, 1920 (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1221
    - Interior elevations - Conservatory, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1222
    - Plan and full scale detail of Pump House, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1223
      Scale: 1"=1'; Full
    - Plan showing location of posts for grape arbor, 1917 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1224
    - Details of court and veranda, Undated (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1225
    - Details of court balustrade, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1226
    - Plan showing farm wall and fence arrangement, 1924 (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1227
    - Plan and details of rose garden, 1917 (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1228
    - Details of gates, Undated (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1229
    - Revised plan of east terrace, 1916 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1230
    - Sketch plan of area about entrance, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1231
    - Plan of terraces, Undated (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1232
    - Details for arbor, Undated (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1233
    - Details of East Terrace, 1916 (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1234
    - Details at overlook and Tennis courts, 1916 (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1235
      Scale: 1/8"=1'; 1/4"=1'; 1/2"=1'
    - Details of entrance court, 1917 (Folder 40)
      Sheet # 1236
      Scale: 1/2"=1'; 3"=1'
    - Plan and elevation of Laundry, 1922 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1237
    - Plan of area at farm entrance, 1924 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1238
    - Window details for stable, 1924 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1239
      Scale: Full; 1/2"=1'
    - Stall plan for stable, 1923 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1240
    - Sketch no. 2 -Layout of owner's suite, 1920 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1241
    - Details of rebuilt main stairs, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1242
    - Sketch plan - New dining room, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1243
    - Bird house and sig post design, 1925 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1244
    - West elevation - East wing addition, 1920 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1245
    - Dining room addition, Undated (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1246
    - Plan of court and dining room showing new axis, Undated (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1247
    - Detail of step and heating trench, Undated (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1248
    - Fireplace details in addition, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1249
    - Second floor plan - East wing addition, 1920 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1250
    - Road elevation - Gardener's cottage, Undated (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1251
    - Stair details, 1920 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1252
    - Interior elevations, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1253
    - Interior elevations - Chamber #1 and Bath #2, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1254
    - Interior elevations, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1255
    - Interior elevations, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1256
    - Interior elevations, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1257
    - Partial first floor plan - Existing condition, 1917 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1258
    - Details of New Dining room, 1921 (Box 44)
      Sheet # 1259
    - Detail of paneling for dining room, 1921 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1667
    - Details of doors (folding) and jamb - dining room, 1921 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1668
    - Details of dormers for low wing, 1921 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1669
    - Detail of sleeping porch, casement windows, Undated (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1670
    - East elevation (East wing additions), 1920 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1671
    - North elevation (East wing addition), 1920 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1672
    - South elevation (East wing addition), 1920 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1673
    - Detail of bell tower - kitchen wing, 1921 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1674
    - Details of stone floor for new dining room, 1921 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1675
    - Interior of new dining room, 1921 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1676
    - Service alterations and additions, 1926 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1677
  - Shwab, Mr. & Mrs. George C. Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Preliminary study for development of property (by H. S.), 1928 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1718
  - Shwab, Hugh Location: Unspecified
    - Stone vase on gate caps, 1923 (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1316
      Format: Tissue paper
    - Sketches of gate, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1317
    - Sketches of gate, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1318
    - Sketches of gate, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1319
    - Sketch of gate, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1320
    - Sketch of gate, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1321
    - Sketch of gate, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1322
  - Sidway, Ralph Location: Grand Island
    - Planting plan made on job by field - garden, 1915 (Folder 45)
      Sheet # 1557
  - Smith, Everett Location: Schenectady, New York
    - Sketch for entrance, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1864
    - Sketch for entrance, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1865
  - Location: Niskayuna, New York
    - Map of land on Balltown Road, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1956
    - Planting plan, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1957
  - Snyder, Mr. and Mrs. William P. Location: Sewickley, Pennsylvania
    - Perspective of steps - Scheme "A", Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 837
    - Perspective of steps between terraces "B" and "C", Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 843
    - Perspective sketch of Second Terrace, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 851
  - Stahelin, Albert J. Location: Long Lake, Bloomfield Township, Michigan
    - Topographical survey and plan keys, by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1925 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 643
    - Plan of foundation and drainage, by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 644
    - Plan of basement, by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 645
    - Plan of first floor by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 646
    - Plan of second by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 647
    - Plan of roof by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 648
    - Section through House "A-A", by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 649
    - South elevation, by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 650
    - North elevation, by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 651
    - East and west elevations, by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 652
    - Sections "B-B", "C-C" and :D-D", by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 653
    - Elevations of interiors, by architect George D. Mason & Co., Undated (Box 27)
      Sheet # 654
    - Plan of first floor framing, by architect George D. Mason & Co., 1924 (Box 27)
      Sheet # 655
    - Study for property management, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 656
    - Study for arrangement of property, Undated (Box 28)
      Sheet # 657
    - Rider - Alternative garden study, 1925 (Box 28)
      Sheet # 658
    - Topographical survey, 1924 (Box 28)
      Sheet # 659
    - Preliminary study for arrangement, 1925 (Box 28)
      Sheet # 660
    - Survey of existing conditions, 1925 (Box 28)
      Sheet # 661
  - St. Ann's Cemetery Location: Hornell, New York
    - Arrangement of grounds, 1907 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1807
    - Lot and planting plan, c. 1908 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1808
    - Topographic survey, c. 1908 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1809
      Condition:Poor to Good
    - Grading plan, 1908 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1810
    - Lot and planting plan, 1908 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1811
  - Statler, E. M., Esq. Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Sketch of Site arrangement, Undated (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 236
    - Planting plan, 1912 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 237
    - Plan of Site arrangement, 1910 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 238
    - Planting Plan, 1911 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 239
    - Foundation Plan, 1910 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 240
    - Piping Plan, Undated (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 241
    - Quarter inch scale drawings of wall, Undated (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 242
    - Details and sections of Garden, 1910 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 243
    - Rough sketch of garden details, Undated (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 244
    - Details of Circular pool, elliptical steps with pool and fountain, 1910 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 245
    - Quarter inch scale drawings of wall, Undated (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 246
    - Preliminary plan of arrangement, Undated (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 247